<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-4166" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">Where Is The Best Ranch in Blacksburg?</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc ">Almost every restaurant in Blacksburg serves ranch... but that doesn't mean every restaurant in Blacksburg is good at it.</shortdesc><body class="- topic/body "><p class="- topic/p ">Ranch dressing is a popular dipping sauce and salad dressing that wields the potential to make or break a meal. An order of hot wings is nothing without a good cup of ranch on the side, and a house salad is just lettuce and some croutons without it. Most restaurants in Blacksburg offer ranch as a sauce option, but not all of these restaurants provide high quality, worthwhile dipping ranch.</p><p class="- topic/p ">Ranch preferences are ultimately subjective; my ranch of choice may be different from yours. For reference, my ranking is based on a scale of ranch quality determined by similarity to purchasable ranch dressings. The highest quality of ranch is comparable to Ken's buttermilk ranch dressing. Ranch that earns the highest quality of ranking will be similar to Ken's in terms of consistency and flavor.</p><p class="- topic/p "><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Ken's Buttermilk Ranch Dressing (the best ranch)</title><image href="kensbuttermilkranch.jpeg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">Image of a bottle of Ken's Buttermilk Ranch</alt></image></fig></p><p class="- topic/p ">The worst quality of ranch is comparable to Hidden Valley Easy Squeeze Ranch. I'd like to stress again that ranch ranking is subjective. But this is low quality ranch. I think "Easy Squeeze" says enough...</p><p class="- topic/p "><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Hidden Valley Easy Squeeze Ranch</title><image href="hiddenvalleyranch.jpeg" class="- topic/image "/></fig></p><p class="- topic/p ">Throughout my rankings, I will reference these two ranches as the highest and lowest quality a restaurant ranch can reach.  Read on to find out what I consider the best ranch in Blacksburg! May the best ranch win!</p></body></topic>